And today, we're going to learn how to set up a drum kit.
So now that all the drums are set up and we've set up our hi-hat stand, we're going to set up our first crash cymbal stand.
Same concept, loosen the wing nut and spread the legs to a nice sturdy situation.
And we're going to tighten it up.
Now, what you want to do here - this is kind of important - you want to take this first leg or one leg and you want to put it facing the inside of your drum set or facing where you're going to be sitting, because when you hit it from that angle you don't want it to tip over.
See if you'd hit it from here, there's a possibility that it could tip.
So we set it there.
That's a good place right now for it.
And now, we have to extend it.
So we can take this, loosen it, and we're going to tighten that.
We're just eyeballing this right now.
We will have to definitely adjust.
And I'm going to take this one and extend it a little bit more.
And then this is the boom, and then this is the head.
We'll loosen--go ahead and loosen both of those and get the head to where you think it's close enough to an angle--a good angle, and then the boom and tighten.
I'm just eyeballing it.
I think that is pretty close for right now.